import { TagQuestion } from '../model/tag-question';

export const TAG_QUESTIONS: TagQuestion[] = [
    {question: "She is accountant,", response: "isn't she"},
    {question: "I'm here,", response: "aren't I"},
    {question: "You and I are busy right now,", response: "aren't we"},
    {question: "It isn't very windy today,", response: "is it"},
    {question: "I'm cooking tonight,", response: "aren't I"},
    {question: "He's not a baby,", response: "is he"},
    {question: "It'll be all right,", response: "won't it"},
    {question: "Laura's still got short hair,", response: "doesn't she"},
    {question: "She doesn't feel well,", response: "does she"},
    {question: "They left early,", response: "didn't they"},
    {question: "She didn't feel well yesterday,", response: "did she"},
    {question: "They've left early,", response: "haven't they"}
];